Now, the last scenario which is the best scenario,
现在是最后一种情形了 也是最佳情形
if the user grants us permission and status, will become granted.
用户授予了权限 status 变成 granted
So what we want to do in this case,
在这种情形下 我们将...
I'm just going to go and paste some styles down here again,
我在这里粘贴一些样式
so you don't have to see that.
不再一一细说了
Basically, what we have is a container,
就是添加了容器
some font stuff, direction which is going to be purple,
字体设置 direction 将为 purple
some more containers. You can check that out if you want to.
其他一些容器 你可以自己看看这些样式
So now, inside of this section down here what we're going to do
现在转到这个部分
is the container is going to be styles.container, the main view.
将该 container 的 style 设为 styles.container 作为主视图
And then, now what we want to do,
然后
let's have a view here.
在这里添加一个 View
And again what we're building in this section,
我们在这里要构建的
is this UI right here.
是这部分 UI
So in this section which is going to be our styles.directioncontainer section,
在此部分 将 style 设为 styles.directionContainer
what we want to show is some text that says, you're heading.
我们想显示以下文本：You're heading
And then, we want to give this a style of styles.header.
将 style 设为 styles.header
And then, below that,
然后在下面再添加一些文本
some more text which is the actual direction that we are heading.
也就是我们的实际朝向
In this case, we'll just hard code north.
这里 我们将方向硬编码为 North
It's going to be styles.direction.
将 style 设为 styles.direction
So this section looks great.
这部分看起来不错
Below that what we want to do,
在它下面
is now we want to have this metric section down here.
我们想显示这部分指标
So what we can do is have another view which
添加另一个视图
is going to have a style of styles.metriccontainer.
将 style 设为 styles.metricContainer
And then inside of here,
然后在这里面
we are going to have a few different things,
添加几项不同的内容
a view with a style of styles.metric and then a text.
添加一个视图 将 style 设为 styles.metric
Again, this is going to be
然后是一个文本
kind of a boring video because we are just building out this UI,
这部分视频内容有点枯燥 因为我们只是在构建这一 UI
so if you want to do this on your own,
如果你想自己构建的话
by all means feel free to.
完全可以
But this text is going to have a style of,
这个文本将有一个样式
is going to have two styles.
将有两个样式
Styles.header and then we will give it a color of whites.
输入 styles.header 然后将 color 设为 white
And then what it's going to say is altitude.
文本内容为 Altitude
And then below this,
下面的内容
it's going to be very similar,
非常相似
so we can just copy and paste this.
可以直接复制粘贴这段代码
Instead of header, it's going to be sub header and we will just have,
将 header 改为 subHeader
let's say, 200 feet will also hard code that.
将这里硬编码为  Feet
And then now, let's go ahead and copy and paste
下面的设置很相似
this because this next one is going to be similar.
直接复制粘贴这段代码
We have metric and then we have styles white.
包括 metric 和样式 white
Instead of saying altitude,
但是 将这里的 Altitude
this is going to say speed.
改为 Speed
And then instead of saying 200 feet,
并将这里的  feet
this can say, let's say,
改为  MPH
300 miles per hour. All right.
好了
This looks pretty good. Let's go ahead and look to see if this is working.
看起来不错 看看应用是否可行
There we go. So even though the state is hard coded now,
虽然暂时状态是硬编码的
the UI looks pretty good.
但是 UI 看起来很棒